

SUMMARY

Short summary: I'm a hard-working, detail-oriented dedicated and responsible person.

Very excited about the career change I made in IT industry and eager to perform and demonstrate my qualities.

Awards & Recognition: Certified Web Developer, Codecademy Certificates of completion for HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

CONTACT INFORMATION

Address: Floresti, CJ, Romania

Tel: +(40) 744 301-841

Email: emanuel.caradan@gmail.com **Site:** https://manu-caradan.web.app

https://www.linkedin.com/in/emanuel-caradan

https://github.com/cmanu07

SKILLS

Attention to Detail, Self-management, Punctuality Problem-solving, Responsibility, Teamwork Computer Skills, Microsoft Office

HTML - 55%

CSS / Bootstrap - 55%

JavaScript - 50%

React - 40%

PHP - 30%

SQL - 50%

EMANUEL CARADAN

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

ERP Concept Solutions SRL

SQL Developer / January 2024 - Present

Vitacom Electronics SRL

IT Support / July 2023 - December 2023

• ERP Software platform with Magento site integration, SQL databases management, Excel

FutureWorkForce SRL

RPA Developer Intern / March 2023 - April 2023

FastTrack IT - certified programming courses

Certified Graduate / November 2021 - June 2022

• Completed training for HTML, CSS and Bootstrap, JavaScript and React also in backend section PHP and MySQL.

Kruk România SRL

Financial Advisor / November 2013 - November 2021

Banca Românească SA

Credit Consultant / July 2013 - November 2013

Banca Comercială Carpatica SA

Account Administrator / August 2008 - June 2013

EDUCATION

Web Development

FastTrack IT - certified programming courses Nov 2021 - Jun 2022

Finance and Banking

University "Babeș-Bolyai" - Cluj-Napoca FSEGA, 2005 - 2008

Recommendation for Emanuel CARADAN

Emanuel (a.k.a. Manu) graduated from the Web Development course I teach and I can testify he's a passionate learner, very responsible and a solution driven person. He was particularly interested in front-end development. With a keen eye for the web page design, Manu solved the projects I gave to the class, trying to make the interface as user-friendly as possible.

Also, he always tried to understand better and deeper the web development topics I presented to them. When facing a "jam", Manu was not afraid to ask for help in order to get the things done.

I would definitely recommend Manu as a web developer.

Sincerely,

Daniel FILIPAŞ, WebDev trainer

June 10, 2022